{
    "subject": "resource/Leona_Lewis",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Leona Lewis",
    "human_readable": "Leona Lewis is labeled as Leona Lewis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9059807658195496,
            "question": "Who is Leona Lewis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8744761347770691,
            "question": "What is Leona Lewis known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8523681163787842,
            "question": "Is Leona Lewis a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.80326247215271,
            "question": "Where is Leona Lewis from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6475571393966675,
            "question": "Has Leona Lewis acted in any movies or TV shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.622352123260498,
            "question": "Is Leona Lewis active in the music industry today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5954729914665222,
            "question": "Are there any notable songs by Leona Lewis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5668792724609375,
            "question": "What genre of music does Leona Lewis perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.515552282333374,
            "question": "What is a defining characteristic of Leona Lewis's musical style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.501709520816803,
            "question": "Has Leona Lewis won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Leona Lewis is labeled as Leona Lewis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8689_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is a defining characteristic of Leona Lewis's musical style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8689_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music does Leona Lewis perform?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8689_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable songs by Leona Lewis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8689_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8689_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8689_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8689_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8689_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8689_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8689_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8689_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8689_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8689_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8689_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents clearly state that Leona Lewis's full name is Leona Louise Lewis and refers to her consistently by the same name throughout the text. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple \"Leona Lewis is a British singer\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents mention that:\n\n* Leona Lewis is a British singer, songwriter, actress, model, and activist. (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8689/re-ranker-msmarco/48.txt)\n* She has won numerous awards for her music career, including three MOBO Awards, two World Music Awards, and a Grammy Award nomination. (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8689/re-ranker-msmarco/32.txt)\n\nThese statements confirm that Leona Lewis is indeed a British singer, making the triple true according to the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"Leona Lewis is labeled as Leona Lewis\" is correct according to the provided documents. All the files mention her by name as \"Leona Lewis.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}